[

	{
		"type": "mc",
		"question": "In what year is Vancouver established?",
		"option":{
			"0": "1666",
			"1": "1766",
			"2": "1866",
			"3": "1901"
			},
		"answer": "2"
	},
	{
		"type": "fill",
		"question": "The city Vancouver were named after Captain _______ Vancouver who was an English officer of the British Royal Navy.",
		"answer": "george"
	},

	{
		"type": "mc",
		"question": "Which river borders vancouver to the south?",
		"option":{
			"0": "Columbia",
			"1": "Fraser",
			"2": "Peace",
			"3": "Liard"
			},
		"answer": "1"
	},
	{
		"type": "mc",
		"question": "How does Vancouver rank in size compared with other Canadian cities?",
		"option":{
			"0": "First",
			"1": "Second",
			"2": "Third",
			"3": "Fourth"
			},
		"answer": "2"
	},
	{
		"type": "fill",
		"question": "In What city is the Vancouver international Airport located?",
		"answer": "richmond"
	},
	{
		"type": "mc",
		"question": "Which city in Metro Vancouver has the 2nd largest population?",
		"option":{
			"0": "Vancouver",
			"1": "Burnaby",
			"2": "Surrey",
			"3": "Richmond"
			},
		"answer": "2"
	},
	{
		"type": "mc",
		"question": "Which city is NOT part of Metro Vancouver?",
		"option":{
			"0": "Maple Ridge",
			"1": "Langley",
			"2": "Pitt Meadows",
			"3": "None of the above"
			},
		"answer": "3"
	},
	{
		"type": "mc",
		"question": "Vancouver is located between the Street of Georgia and?",
		"option":{
			"0": "Coast Mountains",
			"1": "East Mountains",
			"2": "West Mountains",
			"3": "Riverwood Mountains"
			},
		"answer": "0"
	},
	{
		"type": "mc",
		"question": "Vancouver is the largest metropolitan area in western Canada and the what largest in the country?",
		"option":{
			"0": "2nd",
			"1": "3rd",
			"2": "4th",
			"3": "5th"
			},
		"answer": "1"
	},
	{
		"type": "mc",
		"question": "Which province is Vancouver part of?",
		"option":{
			"0": "British Columbia",
			"1": "Alberta",
			"2": "Yukon",
			"3": "Ontario"
			},
		"answer": "0"
	},
	{
		"type": "check",
		"question": "What are the two biggest University in Metro Vancouver?",
		"option":{
			"0": "Capilano University",
			"1": "Simon Fraser University",
			"2": "University of Billion Chinese",
			"3": "University of British Columbia"			
			},
		"answer": "13"
	},
	{
		"type": "check",
		"question": "Simon Fraser University has campuses in 3 different cities. What are they? (Checkbox question)",
		"option":{
			"0": "Surrey",
			"1": "Vancouver",
			"2": "Richmond",
			"3": "West Vancouver",
			"4": "White Rock",
			"5": "Burnaby",
			"6": "Langley",
			"7": "Abbotsford",
			"8": "Toronto",
			"9": "Okanagan"
			},
		"answer": "015"
	},
	{
		"type": "mc",
		"question": "Which of the following parks is located in Vancouver",
		"option":{
			"0": "Stanley Park",
			"1": "Butchart Gardens",
			"2": "Bear Creek Park",
			"3": "Tryndamere Park"
			},
		"answer": "0"
	},
	{
		"type": "mc",
		"question": "Which of these roads is not found in Vancouver?",
		"option":{
			"0": "Main Street",
			"1": "Broadway",
			"2": "Commercial",
			"3": "King George Highway"
			},
		"answer": "3"
	},
	{
		"type": "mc",
		"question": "Which of these places is located about 30 minutes car ride away from Vancouver?",
		"option":{
			"0": "Surrey",
			"1": "Kamloops",
			"2": "Kelowna",
			"3": "Merritt"
			},
		"answer": "0"
	},
	{
		"type": "fill",
		"question": "Science World is located on _____ Street",
		"answer": "quebec"
	}
]




